懒人游戏美食评测
Lazy Game Food Reviews
So yeah I don't have like a whole lot of food supplies and things at the moment，
现在我家里没有那么多吃的
I got to go and just brave the world and grocery shop sometime soon.
我该勇敢地跑出去到杂货店买点了
But I do have some of this bread.
但是我家里还是有些面包
It's just bread, man. These days by what I can get,
就是普通的面包啊，同志们。那时还能随便买时搞来的
and it didn't have what I was looking for.
而且这上面没有我想要的
So you know，this will do because I'm just gonna make an egg sandwich.
鉴于此情况，我只能做点鸡蛋三明治了
I don't have any meat but I do have some eggs left.
我家没有肉了，但还有鸡蛋
So let's toast this.
现在咱就来烤下面包
Yeah, it's like a toasty enough.
火候应该到了
That's toast, set that aside and get the eggs going.
这就是吐司了。放旁边备用，现在来处理鸡蛋
So I've got a little bit of butter left. That's enough.
黄油所剩无几，但应该够了
Just got a medium heat going on here 'cause I'm just gonna scramble them, and make them into a form suitable for sandwich.
开中火，因为我要炒鸡蛋，让其成型以放在三明治中
And just sort of mix it all right here, why not?
然后就这样把它们都炒在一起，为何不呢？
We'll be seasoning after it's all scrambled up.
鸡蛋等炒完后再调味
Well yeah! Oh light and fluffy it looks.
好极了！看上去轻盈蓬松:-)
Like exactly when I'm going for sale.
一会卖相十分不错
The only Duke's mayonnaise size they had at the store last time
上回去超市买的Duke牌蛋黄酱
was this gigantic one, all the others were sold out.
只有这种大罐装的，剩下的都卖没了:-(
So this will last me for a very long time.
所以这个够我吃很长时间的了
Just a little bit dukes.
加一点就行
And also got a bit minced garlic from
再来一点蒜末
I don't know what else I was making from other time.
我忘了啥时搞来的了
But it's still good, I'm gonna use it.
但是这是个好玩意，我要用点
Just a little bit...
仅需一点......
Now it's our egg.
鸡蛋现在登场
Yeah man, love egg sandwiches.
好极了！看上去真耐人:-)
Alright let's season this sucker a little bit, and I got some basil.
好的，现在开始调味。先来点罗勒（一种香叶）
Always a good thing.
拿它调味准没错
And so, this curry salt. I rather enjoy this.
然后是这个咖喱盐，我十分喜欢
Oh crap, that's too much.
该死，倒多了:-(
Well I don't enjoy that much, just a little bit.
放多了就不好了，放一点就行
And of course, some ground peppercorn.
当然，再来点胡椒粉。
Good bit of that. Oh yeah!
放点就行。好极了
Yeah, I got some non-smoked provolone just in package.
好的，这是一包没熏过的Provolone（一种干酪）
Normally I would prefer like a sharp cheddar or something,
一般来说，我更愿意要点切过的Chadder（另一种干酪）
but you eh... better not to be a chooser right now.
但现在呢......就别挑挑拣拣了
Alright, melt this down.
好的，现在拿火烤化它
Oh yeah.
Oh♂yeah
And that'll do it man, wonderful simple little egg sandwich.
然后三明治就做完了:-)
Provolone... Garlic... Basil... Dukes... Yeah, can't go wrong.
干酪啊，蒜末啊，香叶啊，蛋黄酱啊......味道错不了的:-)
Woo, there's some soild egg.
好极了，炒好的鸡蛋
Mmm... and it smells good. Garlic... Cheese... Egg... yes.
嗯~真是挺香的。蒜末啊，干酪啊，鸡蛋啊......好极了:-)
So I don't have pickles...
好吧，今天没有腌黄瓜:-P
I don't even have chips, do I? Wait, no! I do!
我甚至连薯片都没有，是吧......等会，我有！
Oh, I forgot I had it.
我忘了我还有;-P
And they're technically expired but that's okay.
虽然它刚刚过期，但应该没事
That's some holiday brand Chipz natural flavor chips.
这些是Holiday牌（假日牌）Chipz原味薯片
Brought this back from their recent trip.
最近出去玩时买回来的
There apparently distributed in Jamaica,
这里写的是牙买加生产的，（Hermes:这个上税了吗？）
but you can find these all over the place.
但是这哪里都有卖的。
So anyway, that's where they're from.
呃，反正是这个来头啦
Yeah, these are fascinating chips because
是啊，这是包不错的薯片
the consistency is almost Pringle like
因为这个和Pringle牌薯片长得差不多
but they have a shape that stand out.
但是它们长相出众
Lay these things.
把他们放在这里
Right they neat.
好极了
I couldn't help myself.
控制不住，先尝点了
They're so light, extremely crunchy, and like no salt basically.
它们又轻又脆，基本没有盐分
I mean there is salt but it's very minimal.
我是说，有盐但是很少
I guess I'm just standing here and eating this.
我想我就站这儿吃吧
I don't feel like moving the camera.
我不太想动相机
So anyway the chips, yeah, the good chips.
那么这些薯片呢，是相当好的
You remind me of um... not quite Pringles,
当然，这个和Pringles牌的毕竟不同
but you know they're getting there.
但是这质量也差不多了
The more crunchy than that.
这比那个更脆
almost like those Lay's, which are those thins or something,
这个和乐事的一样薄
but still even crankier than that, and even lighter on the salt.
但是这个比那个脆，而且盐分更少
And they're smaller.
而且它们更小:-)
Yeah anyway, they're fun.
无论如何，这样一口一个很好玩
Alright yeah, those kiss ass sandwich.
现在再来看看这个超好的三明治
That is congealed into a solid lump in the middle, oh man.
这炒鸡蛋的中间没溏心，很好
Mmm, so effective.
嗯，味道不错:-)
Yeah, again I really do prefer like a sharp cheddar of some kind on here.
当然，我更乐意来点切过的Chedder放这里
Because you missed the provolone entirely.
因为你们完全错过了Provolone
You can tell it's there but just barely.
你可以说这个差不多，但是它们间也就一点相似
And that garlic just gone through everything and I love that.
那个蒜末浸染了所有东西，我很喜欢
Without garlic this would be rather bland.
没有蒜末，就食之无味了:-(
It's just such a tasty little non full thing.
这个味道不错的小玩意
Crispy delivery mechanism.
来个薯片传送机:-)
You know what? It is way better with those.
你知道吗，这样吃更好
That's what I'm talking about.
这样吃才好:-)
I mean any kind of chips will do,
当然啥薯片都能这么吃
but not preferably something that's light on seasoning or salt
但是这不会给三明治提升口味
because there's that already on the sandwich.
因为三明治上有调料和盐了
Just adding that crunch though, YES!
这只会在三明治上平添一股脆劲:-)
Especially in lieu with pickles.
尤其是没有腌黄瓜时
Well uh, off to go and get some groceries, see what I can find out there.
好的，现在该去超市，看看能买点啥
Hope everybody is staying safe and
希望大家健康安好
it's healthy inside as possible.
没事尽量少出门
I hope you're hungry now because I am.
希望大家都馋了，因为我馋了:-)
Mmm~
本视频SuperBart翻译，原作者LGR发布于2020-4-17